export const languages = {
    'Icelandic': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Ég er hermaður, ekki málaliði og ég veit hvernig stríð er háð', 
            'Það eru tveir hvítir fuglar sem fljúga í burtu', 
            'það lyktar of mikið af sigri, opnaðu gluggann', 
            'Ég spring ókeypis fyrir málstaðinn', 
            'Ég segi það of mikið eins og fólkið sem les'
        ],
        'answer': ['icelandic', 'Iceland']
    },
    'Spanish': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Sociedad decadente, soy el futuro alcalde del XIV.', 
            'Fue en pleno tragaluz donde lo puso el Don.', 
            'Paga muy bien a tu cirujano para romper el hechizo del envejecimiento', 
            'El famoso actor que una vez conocimos parece paranoico y ahora está en espiral', 
            'Un patético maestro manipulador, ahora puedo oler las historias sobre ti'
        ],
        'answer': ['spanish', 'Spain']
    },
    'French': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'J\'suis retombé dedans, faut pas l\'dire aux autres', 
            'Je peux pas taper plus fort sur eux, non, ce serait sadique', 
            'Les années passent, bientôt la greffe de cheveux', 
            'Merci pour votre soutien et votre aide.', 
            'armagnac est tellement beau que je pourrais lui faire des bébés'
        ],
        'answer': ['french', 'France']
    },
    'German': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Hart zu dir, weil hart zu mir selbst', 
            'Jeder möchte so ausbrechen wie der Typ aus Degrassi', 
            'Ich hatte mein weißes Hemd angezogen, sie zerstören all diese kleinen Flecken', 
            'Zehn Jahre später bin ich nicht älter, ich bin mehr OG', 
            'Du denkst wahrscheinlich, dass es dir jetzt besser geht, jetzt besser'
        ],
        'answer': ['german', 'Germany']
    },
    'Italian': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Lo dici solo perché non sono qui', 
            'Però conoscevi tutti i miei zii e le mie zie', 
            'Non vedevamo l\'ora che arrivasse il resto della nostra vita', 
            'Tenevo la mia foto appesa accanto al tuo letto', 
            'Adesso è nel tuo comò con i calzini che non ti piacciono'
        ],
        'answer': ['italian', 'Italy']
    },
    'Portuguese': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Todo mundo se foi, mas ninguém vai embora, ninguém saiu, exceto nós', 
            'Tentando perseguir um sentimento, mas nunca sentiremos isso', 
            'Você diz que quer me ver, mas não pode agora', 
            'Sim, Hollywood está sangrando, mas chamamos isso de lar', 
            'Lá fora, o céu de inverno fica cinza'
        ],
        'answer': ['portuguese', 'Portugal']
    },
    'Dutch': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'in de ochtend, de zon tegenhoudend met de tinten', 
            'Ze moet haar pols controleren om tegen zichzelf te zeggen dat het goed met haar gaat', 
            'Ik laat zien, vind je het leuk wat je ziet ?', 
            'Ik wou dat ik kon gaan, oh, ik verlies de hoop', 
            'Ondanks al deze demonen, wou ik dat ik gewoon naar huis kon gaan'
        ],
        'answer': ['dutch', 'Netherlands']
    },
    'Swedish': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Vi har slut på skäl, men vi kan inte släppa taget', 
            'Det här kan vara natten som mina drömmar kan låta mig veta', 
            'Du kan ta med en kula, ta med ett svärd, ta med ett bårhus', 
            'Jag känner igen ditt falska förtroende och kalkylerade löften, allt i ditt samtal', 
            'Titta galet på mig för jag bjöd inte in dig'
        ],
        'answer': ['swedish', 'Sweden']
    },
    'Danish': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Fordærv en mands hjerte med en gave, på den måde finder du ud af, hvem du har med at gøre', 
            'Hud dækket af ego kommer til at tale som om du er involveret', 
            'Er det alt og hvad du håbede på', 
            'At drage konklusioner, som om du har en Parsons-grad eller noget', 
            'Jeg vil tilbage til de dage, hvor du elskede mig for intet andet end det, du kunne se'
        ],
        'answer': ['danish', 'Denmark']
    },
    'Norwegian': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Tekstene våre føles som en spektakulær kamp, temperamentet ditt er kortere, og jeg føler det', 
            'Hun tror ikke på stjerneskudd, men hun tror på sko og biler', 
            'Tregulv i den nye leiligheten couture fra butikkens avdelinger', 
            'Du liker mer å starte dritt jeg er mer av turene til florida', 
            'Rett fra en side av favorittforfatteren din og været så luftig'
        ],
        'answer': ['norwegian', 'Norway']
    },
    'Finnish': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Ja jos joku olisi kertonut minulle kuukausi sitten eturintamassa, joo, en haluaisi tietää', 
            'Veli, kaikki syttyy tuleen, jos syljen virtauksen lammastarhassa vapautan pedon', 
            'Älä häpeä, soita trumpettia, heitä kukkia kun shiznit menee ohi', 
            'Jokaisella on oma mif\' ja omat sormukset, odotan rahaa ja siitä on pitkä aika', 
            'Tarvitsen rahaa heti, jahda sen kanssa, joka minun pitäisi olla'
        ],
        'answer': ['finnish', 'Finland']
    },
    'Russian': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Они все говорят одно и то же, одинаковыми звуками, танцуют одни и те же слова, одни и те же слова', 
            'мой круг квадратный, ты, твой круг порочный, ты должен быть готов, когда выполняешь свои миссии', 
            'Мы сгибаемся в настоящем, мы сгибались уже в прошлом', 
            'Я не могу найти твой дом, пришли мне информацию, проезжая через закрытый жилой дом', 
            'Узнал, что я приду, отправил своих друзей домой, продолжай пытаться скрыть это, но твои друзья знают'
        ],
        'answer': ['russian', 'Russia']
    },
    'Ukrainian': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Я дзвоню тобі лише тоді, коли пів на шосту Єдиний раз, коли я буду поруч з тобою', 
            'Мені подобається лише коли ти торкаєшся мене, а не відчуваєш мене, коли я погана, це справжня я', 
            'Коли я поганий, це справжній я, так, я дзвоню тобі лише коли пів на шосту', 
            'Я дам вам знати, і будьте простими, намагайтеся продовжувати, не здається таким простим', 
            'пагорби мають очі, Хто ти такий, щоб судити'
        ],
        'answer': ['ukrainian', 'Ukraine']
    },
    'Czech': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'A vím, že ona bude mou smrtí alespoň budeme oba otupělí', 
            'vždycky ze mě dostane to nejlepší to nejhorší teprve přijde', 
            'To nejhorší teprve přijde ale aspoň budeme oba krásní', 
            'Mám pocit, že vy všichni nepotřebujete lásku, potřebujete někoho, kdo by vás mohl mikrořídit', 
            'Chci být doopravdy zamilovaný i když je mi jedno co mě to stojí vyměním cokoli abych se teď cítil'
        ],
        'answer': ['czech', 'Czech Republic']
    },
    'Slovak': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Mám taký pocit, na ktorý nie si zvyknutý prisahám že by som bol pokojný keby nebolo teba', 
            'Keď slnko zapadne všetko vo mne vyvoláva pocit osamelosti áno', 
            'Mal trochu vedľajšiu vec, ale práve teraz je to chlap, ktorý sa snaží cítiť sa dobre vo vnútri, nikdy ma nechce držať', 
            'Rozhýbeš ma, dostaneš ma do rozruchu, ty môj obľúbený tréner poď stlačiť linku', 
            'Posratý stres, to je moja jediná neresť, zbavím sa toho, keď mi povie, či sa cítim dobre'
        ],
        'answer': ['slovak', 'Slovakia']
    },
    'Hungarian': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Felfuttatom megkockáztatom az egészet mintha kockával dobnék Az egészet figyelembe véve ez a második életem', 
            'Mondjuk a ciklusodon, de ő a menstruációján is annyira felpörögtek az asztalok, hogy azt hittem, ez csak csocsó.', 
            'Ez egy kráter vagy űrhajó, fogd be a pofád, ne vessz el semmi szívességet, megfogadom, bármit érsz', 
            'Tévedésből senki sem volt a táskájukban, de hány holttest volt az ágyában', 
            'És tudod, hogy úgy mészárolok le, mintha Jason elpusztítanám, miért kaptad meg biztonságban'
        ],
        'answer': ['hungarian', 'Hungary']
    },
    'Romanian': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Nu știu dacă poate accepta că vrei să mă vezi goală', 
            'Învârtită și udă de parcă ar fi venit de la o fată albă irosită cu acel lichior maro', 
            'Când sunt așa, nu pot fi lângă tine, sunt prea luminat ca să-l estompez', 
            'Sper că știți că sunt persistentă, știți că acest fursec este pentru coacere', 
            'Verificați mesajul fixat pentru a încerca celelalte chestionare'
        ],
        'answer': ['romanian', 'Romania']
    },
    'Bulgarian': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'И знаеш, че съм заклан, сякаш съм Джейсън, разби го, защо го взе на безопасност', 
            'Заседнали в тази парадигма, не вярвайте в рая, това трябва да е адът', 
            'Трябва да има повече, трябва да съм по-болен от тази моя глава натрапчиви мисли, те парализират', 
            'Натрапчиви мисли, те парализират нирвана не е както се рекламира, трябва да има повече, бил съм тук преди', 
            'Животът е по-добър на Сатурн, трябва да прекъсне този модел на отплуване'
        ],
        'answer': ['bulgarian', 'Bulgaria']
    },
    'Serbian': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Живот је бољи на Сатурну мора да прекине овај образац лебдења', 
            'Ако је карма стварно стварна како сам још увек овде изгледа тако неправедно', 
            'Можда грешим, ако има смисла бити добар, где је онда моја награда', 
            'Углавном мислиш да си сада бољи, само то кажеш зато што нисам ту', 
            'Нисам веровао да ће се све завршити на другом месту после Бенза'
        ],
        'answer': ['serbian', 'Serbia']
    },
    'Croatian': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Nisam vjerovao da će završiti sve je došao na drugo mjesto nakon Benza', 
            'Dvadeset svijeća ugasi ih i otvori oči veselili smo se ostatku života', 
            'Prije sam držao moju sliku pored kreveta, a sada je u tvojoj komodi s čarapama koje ti se ne sviđaju', 
            'Znaš da te nikad nisam namjeravao iznevjeriti, iznevjeriti te dao bi ti sve, ne bih ti dao ništa', 
            'Vidio sam te s tvojim drugim tipom činilo se da je prilično cool bio sam tako slomljen zbog tebe'
        ],
        'answer': ['croatian', 'Croatia']
    },
    'Slovenian': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Ne odraščaj v naglici, tvojo mamo bo skrbelo', 
            'Hvala za vso slavo, ostal si boš v spominu, oj hvala vsem junakom večera', 
            'Morajo prebarvati barve, laž se obrabi, resničnost je pred nami, barve kapljajo', 
            'Oče, oprosti mi, bojim se karme, ker zdaj vidim ženske kot nekaj, kar je treba negovati', 
            'Prebil ga bom, moli, da bom premagal obtožbe, ne, očka se ne igraj, ne ko gre za njune hčere'
        ],
        'answer': ['slovenian', 'Slovenia']
    },
    'Albanian': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Mos bëni joga, mos bëni pilates thjesht luani piano dhe përmbahuni në karate', 
            'lutem që trupi juaj të jetë më shumë si i imi, unë lutem që trupi juaj të jetë më shumë si i imi', 
            'Unë lutem që ju të mos i merrni të gjitha kthesat në të njëjtën kohë nën fustanin tuaj, e di që është e përhapur në rrjet', 
            'Të gjitha në komente, doni të vjellni ky është fëmija juaj, ju e doni atë deri në vdekje', 
            'Tani ajo ndërpret klasën dhe duke u varur me miqtë, ju thyeni një gotë dhe e thoni përsëri'
        ],
        'answer': ['albanian', 'Albania']
    },
    'Maltese': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Issa taqta\' l-klassi u tistrieħ mal-ħbieb int tkisser tazza u terġa\' tgħidha', 
            'Ejja nitolbu nistgħu npoġġu dan warajna naħlef li dawn iż-żminijiet huma l-aktar selvaġġi', 
            'Imma l-bieraħ hija mejta, iva, mument ta \'silenzju li jmiss, hi se titlaq il-kulleġġ u mbagħad fuq l-artal', 
            'Tikberx bil-għaġla, ommok tkun inkwetata li kienet kollha parti mill-istorja, anke l-iljieli tal-biża', 
            'Jien iddawwarha għal mostru, iżda l-ebda menages ma nafx kif qed tgħidu, imma ħallihom jisimgħu dan'
        ],
        'answer': ['maltese', 'Malta']
    },
    'Estonian': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Ma muudan ta koletiseks, kuid mitte mingit vaevust ma ei tea, kuidas sa seda ütled, aga las nad kuulevad seda', 
            'Kõik, mida ma kunagi tahtsin, oli must Grand National kurat, kui olete ratsionaalne, andke neile, mida nad küsivad', 
            'Ma võtan G-passi, kurat, vaatan mando it, ah, me jäime väljas ellu, kõik muusikast', 
            'Sa vajad sinust meest, kallis, ma ei saa aru, et maksan su arvet ja panen sind tundma kaitstuna nagu ma saan', 
            'Õpetage sulle midagi, kui vajad parandamist, see on plaan, kullake ära pane oma elu nende imelike meeste kätesse'
        ],
        'answer': ['estonian', 'Estonia']
    },
    'Latvian': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Iemācīt tev kaut ko, ja tev ir vajadzīga korekcija, tāds ir plāns, mazulīt nenodod savu dzīvi šo dīvaino cilvēku rokās', 
            'Vai nav ar manām aktivitātēm? Tad neiesaisties hei, ko, a, cik man sūtīt, nosūtiet tos visus', 
            'Riskējiet vai dodieties ceļojumā, jūs zināt, ka es paklupu pēc sava suņa ar ko tu, pāris seržantu un leitnantu, lai atgrieztos', 
            'Es pārtraucu savu vecmāmiņu, ja viņa to neredz, kā es to redzu, hm man ir liela mute, bet viņam trūkst lielu ideju', 
            'Vai šajā repā nav neviena cita karaļa, viņi ir brāļi un māsas, izņemot mani bērni, viens šāviens, viņi pazūd.'
        ],
        'answer': ['latvian', 'Latvia']
    },
    'Lithuanian': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Aš esu mieste, kur vėliava bus išmesta, tarsi aplink pastatą būtų spyna trukdžių spyna', 
            'Turėdamas tokį kaulą, lyg tai būtų jūros ešerys, taigi, kai išėjau, iš pasirodymo padariau apie 50 tūkst.', 
            'Esu pranašiškas, jie tik apie tai kalba, kaip aš gaunu tai tik gera gelbėti veidą, mačiau kosmetiką', 
            'Kiek galvų turiu paimti, kad išlyginčiau savo estetiką, paskubėčiau ir paauginčiau raumenis.', 
            'Miestas tiesiog padarė jį mielą, tu gali mirti, galiu lažintis, kad jų burna pilna apgaulės, tegul bailiai tai pasako'
        ],
        'answer': ['lithuanian', 'Lithuania']
    },
    'Hindi': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'शहर ने इसे मीठा बना दिया है, आप मर सकते हैं, मुझे यकीन है कि उनके मुंह धोखे से भरे होंगे, इन कायरों को यह बताने दो', 
            'आपके पास जो पैसे हैं, वे आपकी संपत्ति की सुरक्षा के लिए हैं, आपके पास पैसे बचाने के लिए पैसे हैं।', 
            'इस समय, बस इस्मेस्टा में आवेदन करें, टार्सी एपलिंक पेस्टाटे और स्पाइना ट्रकडिज़िक स्पाइना', 
            'वै साजा रेपा नव नेवीना सीता करुआ, विनी इर ब्राई अन मासस, इज़ेमोट मणि बर्नी, विएन्स शाविएन्स, विनी पज़ुद', 
            'इमासिट तेव काउत को, जा तेव इर वजदजिगा कोरेकिजा, टाड्स इर प्लान्स, माजुलिट नेनोडोड सावु डेजिवि शाओ डिवैनो सिल्वेकु रोकास'
        ],
        'answer': ['hindi']
    },
    'Bengali': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'আপনার যদি একটি সমাধানের প্রয়োজন হয় তবে আপনাকে কিছু শেখান যা এই অদ্ভুতদের হাতে আপনার জীবন না দেওয়ার পরিকল্পনা', 
            'আমি ভবিষ্যদ্বাণীপূর্ণ, তারা এটি সম্পর্কে এত কথা বলে, আমি কীভাবে এটির মুখ এত ভালভাবে সংরক্ষণ করতে পারি', 
            'তাকে আমি একটি দৈত্যে পরিণত করি, কিন্তু কোন আপত্তি নেই আমি জানি আপনি কীভাবে বলছেন, তবে তাদের এটি শুনতে দিন', 
            'র্ণ, তারা এটি সম্পর্কে এত কথা ব দেব কিন্তু কোন সমস্যা নেই আমি জানি না আপনি কিভাবে বলছেন তবে তাদের শুনতে দিন', 
            'ভা সাজা রেপা নভ নেভিনা সীতা করুয়া, উইনি ইর ব্রাই উন মাসাস, ইজেমোট মানি বার্নি, ভিয়েন্স শাভিয়েন্স, উইনি পাজুদ'
        ],
        'answer': ['bengali']
    },
    'Tamil': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'வா சஜா ரெபா நவ் நெவினா சீதா கருவா, வினி இர் ப்ராய் அன் மசாஸ், இஸெமோட் மணி பெர்னி, வியன்ஸ் ஷேவியன்ஸ்', 
            'உங்களுக்கு ஒரு தீர்வு தேவைப்பட்டால், இந்த அந்நியர்களின் கைகளில் உங்கள் வாழ்க்கையை விட்டுவிடாமல் இருப்பதைப் ', 
            'நான் தீர்க்கதரிசி, அவர்கள் அதைப் பற்றி அதிகம் பேசுகிறார்கள், அதன் முகத்தை நான் எப்படி நன்றாகப் பாதுகாக்க', 
            'முகத்தை காப்பாற்ற மட்டுமே நல்லது, பார்த்த அழகுசாதனப் பொருட்கள் என் அழகியலை நிலைநிறுத்த நான் எத்தனை', 
            'ஃப்ரீஸ் டேக் விளையாட, குறிக்கப்படாத டிரக்கில் மேலே இழுக்கிறேன் அது கடல் பாஸ் போல எடுக்க எலும்புடன்'
        ],
        'answer': ['tamil']
    },
    'Telugu': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'ఫ్రీజ్ ట్యాగ్‌ని ప్లే చేయడానికి గుర్తు తెలియని ట్రక్కులో పైకి లాగండి సీ బాస్ లాగా తీయడానికి ఎముకతో', 
            'ముఖాన్ని కాపాడుకోవడానికి మాత్రమే మంచిది, నా సౌందర్యాన్ని కాపాడుకోవడానికి నేను ఎన్ని సౌందర్య సాధనాలను చూస్తాను', 
            'వా సజా రెబా నవ్ నెవినా సీతా కరువా, వినీ ఇర్ ప్రై అన్ మసాస్, ఇసెమోట్ మణి బెర్ని, వియన్స్ షావియన్స్', 
            'మీకు పరిష్కారం కావాలంటే, మీ జీవితాన్ని ఈ విచిత్రాల చేతుల్లో పెట్టకుండా ఉండేలా ప్రణాళిక ఏమిటో మీకు నేర్పండి', 
            'మీ వద్ద ఉన్న డబ్బు మీ ఆస్తులను రక్షించడానికి ఉంది, డబ్బు ఆదా చేయడానికి మీకు డబ్బు ఉంది'
        ],
        'answer': ['telugu']
    },
    'Malayalam': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'നിങ്ങളുടെ കൈവശമുള്ള പണം നിങ്ങളുടെ ആസ്തികൾ സംരക്ഷിക്കാൻ ഉണ്ട്, പണം ലാഭിക്കാൻ നിങ്ങൾക്ക് പണമുണ്ട്.', 
            'ആസ്തികൾ സംരക്ഷിക്കാൻ നിങ്ങളുടെ നിങ്ങൾക്ക് പണമുണ്ട്, പണം ലാഭിക്കാൻ നിങ്ങൾക്ക് പണമുണ്ട്', 
            'സീ ബാസിനെപ്പോലെ എടുക്കാൻ എല്ലുകൊണ്ടുള്ള ഫ്രീസ് ടാഗ് കളിക്കാൻ അടയാളപ്പെടുത്താത്ത ട്രക്കിൽ വലിക്കുക', 
            'മുഖം രക്ഷിക്കാൻ മാത്രം നല്ലത്, എൻ്റെ സൗന്ദര്യം സംരക്ഷിക്കാൻ ഞാൻ എത്ര സൗന്ദര്യവർദ്ധക വസ്തുക്കളാണ് ഉപയോഗിക്കുന്നത്', 
            'വാ സജ റേബ നവ് നെവിന സീതാ കരുവാ, വിനി ഇർ പ്രൈ ആൻ മാസസ്, ഇസെമോട്ട് മണി ബെർണി, വിയൻസ് ഷാവിയൻസ്'
        ],
        'answer': ['malayalam']
    },
    'Sinhala': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'ඔබේ වත්කම් ආරක්ෂා කිරීම සඳහා ඔබට මුදල් තිබේ, මුදල් ඉතිරි කර ගැනීම සඳහා ඔබට මුදල් තිබේ', 
            'ඔබට විසඳුමක් අවශ්ය නම්, මෙම රාක්ෂයන් අතින් ඔබේ ජීවිතය තැබීම සැලැස්ම කුමක්දැයි ඉගෙන ගන්න', 
            'බාර්එකක් මෙන් ඇටකටු සමඟ කැටි ටැගය වාදනය කිරීම සඳහා සුළුපටු ට්රක් රථයකින් නවත්වන්න', 
            'මම ඉන්නේ කොඩිය ගසාගෙන යන නගරයේ, එය ගොඩනැගිල්ල වටා ඇති දැඩි පෑඩ්ලොක්', 
            'මේ රැප් එකේ වෙන රජෙක් නෙවෙයි, ඔවුන් සහෝදර සහෝදරියන් මගේ දරුවන් හැර වෙන කිසිවක් නැත, එක් පහරක්, ඔවුන් අතුරුදහන්'
        ],
        'answer': ['sinhala']
    },
    'Korean': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            '그녀는 통제력이 너무 강해, 장난이 아니란 걸 알아차렸어, 십대 때 현관 밖에 있을 때 그녀를 만났어', 
            '그녀는 언젠가 내 잘못을 바로잡고 우리가 어렸을 때부터 정체성을 찾으며 시작한 서류를 보게 될 거라고 말했어요', 
            '하지만 내 손으로 네 허리를 감쌀 때 우리 사이에는 케미스트리가 부족했던 적이 없었어', 
            '마약을 팔거나, 블록을 팔거나, 은행을 털거나 하는 꿈을 꾸던 시절이었죠', 
            '난 너와 사랑에 빠졌어, 너와 무슨 관계인지 몰랐어, 수업 뒤에서 너랑 흥얼거리려고 키스해 줬어'
        ],
        'answer': ['korean', 'korea', 'south korea', 'north korea']
    },
    'Chinese': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            '我爱上了你，不知道你在教室后面亲吻你是怎么回事，只是为了和你一起热闹', 
            '曾经有一段时间，我梦想着卖毒品、卖街区、抢劫银行。', 
            '但当我双手搂住你的腰时，我们之间从来不缺乏化学反应', 
            '她说有一天我会纠正自己的错误，看看我们小时候开始的报纸，找到我们的身份。', 
            '她控制欲极强，我知道这不是玩笑，我十几岁的时候就在前门外遇见了她'
        ],
        'answer': ['chinese', 'china']
    },
    'Malay': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Saya lebih suka mengelakkan masalah tetapi saya mempunyai dua atau tiga tempat jika anda bosan', 
            'Kami tetap terlindung dalam gelembung udara, walaupun selepas hujan lebat', 
            'Saya tidak akan memberitahu anda bahawa saya boleh melakukannya, saya akan pergi atau saya akan diam', 
            'Tidak ada alasan lagi untuk takut daripada bertenang, jika saya memberi anda sejuta, itu bukan untuk pai meringue', 
            'Semasa saya kecil, saya boleh menceritakan reufré dengan semua kisah saya dari masa itu'
        ],
        'answer': ['malay', 'malaysian']
    },
    'Japanese': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            '幼い頃、その時の話をすべてルフレに伝えることができた', 
            '番大切なのはそれを信じることだということを思い出した', 
            'でもそれを信じすぎるクソ野郎は大嫌いだ', 
            'テキスト通りに生きないなら、少なくとも自分の人生を生きなさい、お偉いさん', 
            'ヘルマン・ヘッセの本のように、これを段階的に落としていきます'
        ],
        'answer': ['japanese', 'japan']
    },
    'Irish': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Tá mé ag titim amach céim ar chéim mar atá i leabhar Hermann Hesse', 
            'Lá amháin, líne amháin eile agus níl mé ag caint faoi', 
            'Ná cuir mearbhall ar do chinniúint le scannán, ná lig d\'aon duine tú a thabhairt anuas', 
            'Iad siúd atá thart orainn allais ár lochtanna, faire amach do dhaoine', 
            'Ach ár gcáilíochtaí freisin mar sin coinnímid an dúshraith chéanna'
        ],
        'answer': ['irish', 'ireland']
    },
    'Thai': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'แต่คุณสมบัติของเราก็เช่นกันดังนั้นเราจึงรักษารากฐานเดียวกัน', 
            'คนที่อยู่รอบตัวเราต่างหลั่งเหงื่อให้กับความผิดของเรา ระวังผู้คนด้วย', 
            'อย่าสับสนโชคชะตาของคุณด้วยภาพยนตร์ อย่าให้ใครมาทำให้คุณผิดหวัง', 
            'วันหนึ่งอีกหนึ่งบรรทัดและฉันจะไม่พูดถึงมัน', 
            'ฉันล้มลงไปทีละขั้นเหมือนในหนังสือของแฮร์มันน์ เฮสเส'
        ],
        'answer': ['thai', 'thailand']
    },
    'Vietnamese': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Và giống như một cậu bé lớn, tôi hút nhạc cụ theo ba mươi cách', 
            'Thứ Hai đến Chủ Nhật, cứ quẩn quanh trong đầu tôi', 
            'Cuộc đời tôi là một bộ phim Sundance, đôi khi chẳng có gì xảy ra', 
            'Tôi thích tránh xa rắc rối hơn, nhưng tôi có hai ba plavan nếu bạn thấy chán', 
            'Chúng ta vẫn được che chở trong bong bóng khí, ngay cả sau trận mưa như trút nước'
        ],
        'answer': ['vietnamese', 'vietnam']
    },
    'Indonesian': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Kita tetap terlindung dalam gelembung udara, bahkan setelah hujan lebat', 
            'Saya lebih suka menghindari masalah, tetapi saya punya dua atau tiga plavan jika Anda bosan', 
            'Hidupku seperti film Sundance, terkadang tidak terjadi apa-apa', 
            'Senin hingga Minggu, terus berputar-putar di kepalaku', 
            'Dan seperti anak besar, saya menghisap instrumen itu dengan tiga puluh cara'
        ],
        'answer': ['indonesian', 'indonesia']
    },
    'Tagalog': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Napakaraming madilim na kwento, malaki kung mailuluwa ko sa iyo', 
            'Magkakaroon ng apat na mixtape, sapat na para makamot sa iyong windpipe', 
            'Oo, nag-freeze ang mga katawan, nag-iisa ako, hindi mo alam ang punto ng pagpilit, hindi tulad ng iba', 
            'Kung gagawin ko ito, para sa kinabukasan ko, hindi dahil sa saya ng puso', 
            'Marami akong nasayang na oras sa mga bagay na walang kabuluhan, buti na lang iilan sa mga mahal ko sa buhay ang ninakaw sa akin'
        ],
        'answer': ['Tagalog', 'filipino', 'philippines', 'tagalog']
    },
    'Burmese': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'ကျွန်ုပ်၏စာကြောင်းများရှိ တုံးများကို ရွှေတူးသမားကဲ့သို့ စီရန်ကြိုးစားပါ။', 
            'ငါပြောနေတဲ့အတိုင်း ရက်ပ်ဆိုပေမဲ့ ငါမပြောဝံ့အောင်ရေးတယ်။', 
            'မထွက်ခွာမီ ဤဂိမ်းတွင် မီးပိတ်ပါမည်။', 
            'ဒီအတိုင်းဆက်သွားရင်၊ မင်းကို ဆယ်မိနစ်စာ စာလေးရေးမယ်။', 
            'ကိုယ့်အတွက် စည်းကမ်းတွေ သတ်မှတ်ပြီး ဂိတ်ဆုံးတဲ့အထိ မရပ်ဘူး။'
        ],
        'answer': ['burmese', 'myanmar', 'birmania']
    },
    'Persian': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'من برای خودم قوانینی تعیین کردم و تا رسیدن به پایانه متوقف نشدم', 
            'اگر این روند ادامه پیدا کند، یک نامه ده دقیقه ای برایت می نویسم', 
            'چراغ ها در این بازی قبل از حرکت خاموش می شوند', 
            'من مثل اینکه دارم حرف می زنم رپ می کنم، اما طوری می نویسم که از گفتن آن می ترسم', 
            'قوانینی را برای خود تعیین کنید و تا پایان دروازه متوقف نشوید'
        ],
        'answer': ['persian', 'farci']
    },
    'Arabic': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'ضع قواعد لنفسك ولا تتوقف حتى نهاية البوابة', 
            'لا أحد يعرفني أفضل من صفحتي على ويكيبيديا', 
            'حاول فرز شذرات جملك مثل المنقب عن الذهب', 
            'لا تكذب على نفسك، فأنت ترى أنني الأكثر أصالة، ولا داعي لقول إنني أحبك حتى تكون رومانسيًا.', 
            'بدون تنقيح، أنا فنان أصور فيلمًا، سأنهي حياتي في بلدة صغيرة جدًا في الأرجنتين'
        ],
        'answer': ['arabic', 'arab', 'arabe']
    },
    'Georgian': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'რეტუშის გარეშე, მე ვარ მხატვარი, რომელიც გადაღებებს ფილმზე', 
            'სიცოცხლეს დავასრულებ არგენტინის ძალიან პატარა ქალაქში', 
            'ამასობაში ხელფასს ვანაწილებ როგორც ბოსი მუდამ დედა კომპანიისადმი ლოიალური დარონივით', 
            'სიყვარული კი მაშინებს, ძალიან ბევრი მეგობარი მინახავს იატაკზე, ეჭვით ვცხოვრობ, ის ჩემი ყველაზე ერთგული ოთახია', 
            'გადაუწყვეტელი თაობა, რომლის უარყოფა შეუძლებელია და ხშირად, პირველი პაემნებიც უკანასკნელია'
        ],
        'answer': ['Georgian', 'Georgia']
    },
    'Afrikaans': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Ek weet egter dat daar iemand aan die einde van my ry vir my wag, hoop is nie net in boeke nie', 
            'En ek moet vertrou, en leef met my wonde dit is dit, ek is in \'n beswyming, ek het pas twee-en-dertig maatreëls geslaag', 
            'Ek jongleren met improv, en jy sien, al my pro-probleme het nie \'n tema nie', 
            'groot ou En dit is die hart wat altyd die tempo klop', 
            'Om aan die son te raak, neem ek icarus se pen, ek luister na die produksie, verbeel my die padre wat kitaar speel'
        ],
        'answer': ['Afrikaans', 'South Africa']
    },
    'Hawaiian': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'No ka hoʻopā ʻana i ka lā, lawe wau i ka peni a icarus, hoʻolohe wau i ka hana, noʻonoʻo i ka padre e hoʻokani ana i ke kīkā', 
            'E haʻi mai ʻo ia iaʻu: "Ua ʻoi aku kou wela", ʻakaʻaka ʻo ia a ʻōlelo mai e paipai iaʻu e hakakā, makemake ʻo Oli ka lehulehu i ke koko', 
            'Hāʻawi wau i ka sensational, me ka ʻole o nā , ke manaʻoʻiʻo nei au i ka mana o ka noʻonoʻo', 
            'A hilinaʻi au i ka nui o ka lāhui kanaka, i kēia ao kahiko i ʻike mai iaʻu i hānau ʻia, i ka nani o ke ʻano', 
            'Makaʻu wau i ke kanakolu, hoʻopau ka manawa iaʻu, makemake au e noho kamaliʻi ke ʻike au i nā mākua.'
        ],
        'answer': ['Hawaiian', 'Hawaii', 'Hawai']
    },
    'Hebrew': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'אני מפחד מגיל שלושים, הזמן מבזבז אותי, אני רוצה להיות ילד כשאני רואה את ההורים שלי.', 
            'ואני מאמין בגדולתו של המין האנושי, בעולם העתיק הזה שראה אותי נולד, ביופיו של הטבע', 
            'אני נותן סנסציוני, בלי אבני חן, אני מאמין בכוח הדמיון', 
            'הוא יגיד לי: "אתה יותר לוהט", הוא צוחק ואומר לעודד אותי להילחם, אולי הקהל רוצה דם', 
            'כדי לגעת בשמש, אני לוקח את העט של איקרוס, אני מקשיב לעבודה, מדמיין את הפאדר מנגן בגיטרה'
        ],
        'answer': ['Hebrew', 'Israel']
    },
    'Armenian': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Արևին դիպչելու համար վերցնում եմ իկարուսի գրիչը, լսում եմ ստեղծագործությունը, պատկերացրեք, թե ինչպես է հայրիկը կիթառ է նվագում', 
            'Ինձ կասի. «Դու ավելի տաք ես», ծիծաղում է ու ասում, որ ինձ քաջալերես, որ կռվեմ, Օլի ամբոխը արյուն է ուզում։', 
            'Եվ ես հավատում եմ մարդկային ցեղի մեծությանը, այս հին աշխարհին, որը տեսել է ինձ ծնված, բնության գեղեցկությանը:', 
            'Բայց գրչի շնորհիվ ես օգնում եմ շատ տղաների, ովքեր իմ ոտանավորներն են զգում որպես փոքրիկ միջոց', 
            'Երեկ տեսա, որ հազարավոր ծիծեռնակներ իջնում ​​էին երկնքից, ձայնագրում էի ինձ դիկտաֆոնի վրա և ռեփ եմ անում type-beat-ով։'
        ],
        'answer': ['Armenian', 'Armenia']
    },
    'Catalan': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Massa d\'hora, potser més tard podeu ensenyar-me les coses que sabeu què és sempre que visiti', 
            'Ciutat ventosa, em bufa petons trenta graus, massa fred, així que abraça\'m fort', 
            'Busco la pau, però mira, no aconsegueixo el que necessito per mantenir, aquest joc ximple que juguem', 
            'Perquè dia i nit, el stoner solitari sembla alliberar la seva ment a la nit', 
            'Un dormidor silenciós, no sentiràs ni un pipí, la noia que vol no sembla que el vulgui també'
        ],
        'answer': ['Catalan', 'catalonia']
    },
    'Corsican': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Un dorme silenziu, ùn senterete micca un piu, a zitella ch\'ellu vole ùn pare micca vulè ancu ellu', 
            'Calchì volta, quandu mi puseraghju è lascià veramente registrà, aghju fattu tuttu ciò chì aghju dettu chì avissi, è l\'aghju dettu prima', 
            'Avemu da alimentà questi ghjovani à u metaversu intantu, sò quì à pruvà à scrive un versu', 
            'Perchè aghju finitu di esse extra cù l\'estroverti l\'etichetta si dumandava cumu si deve stà vicinu à Vert', 
            'ùn hà mai pensatu chì aghju da fà queste gammi per travaglià, travagliendu duramente, ma a merda dura ùn hà micca bisognu di travagliu extra'
        ],
        'answer': ['Corsican', 'Corsica', 'Corsia', 'Corsian', 'Corse']
    },
    'Scottish Gaelic': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Cha do smaoinich a-riamh gum faigheadh ​​​​mi na casan sin gu bhith ag obair gu cruaidh, ach chan fheum cac cruaidh obair a bharrachd', 
            'Sin as coireach gu bheil mi a’ nochdadh ann an sweatshirt agus a ’leigeil leis losgadh mise an t-saoghail, tha mi dìreach ag ràdh, leig leis tionndadh', 
            'B’ urrainn dhomh a bhith air aghaidh ach rinn mi an cac seo mar a b’ fheàrr leam, tha fios agam gum bu chòir dhomh a bhith iriosal', 
            'Ann an ùine ghoirid feumaidh mi na droch chleachdaidhean sin a thoirt air falbh cho luath \'s as urrainn dhuinn a thighinn a dh\'fhaighinn an cac a tha sinn a\' cosnadh', 
            'Tha mi creidsinn nuair a tha gaol aig an t-saoghal air fad ort, nach robh aig daoine ach aon dòigh air'
        ],
        'answer': ['Scottish Gaelic', 'Scottish', 'Scotland', 'gaelic', 'scots', 'scots gaelic']
    },
    'Welsh': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Rwy\'n dyfalu pan fydd y byd i gyd yn caru chi, dim ond un ffordd i bobl ei chael', 
            'Yn fyr mae angen i mi roi hwb i\'r arferion drwg hyn mor gyflym ag y gallwn i gael y cachu rydym yn ei ennill', 
            'Roeddwn i\'n gallu mynd ymlaen ond fe wnes i\'r cachu hwn y gorau dwi\'n gwybod y dylwn i fod yn ostyngedig', 
            'Dyna pam dwi\'n ymddangos mewn crys chwys ac yn gadael iddo losgi\'r byd i mi, dwi\'n dweud, gadewch iddo droi', 
            'Ni feddyliodd erioed y byddwn yn cael y coesau hynny i weithio\'n galed, ond nid oes angen gwaith ychwanegol ar cachu caled'
        ],
        'answer': ['welsh', 'wales']
    },
    'Greek': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Αρκετά σύντομα πρέπει να κάνω αυτές τις κακές συνήθειες να κάψουν', 
            'Ξέρω ότι πρέπει να είμαι ταπεινός, αλλά είναι κάτι που απλά δεν έχω μάθει', 
            'Υποθέτω ότι όταν όλος ο κόσμος σε αγαπά, οι άνθρωποι έχουν μόνο έναν τρόπο να ξεχωρίζουν', 
            'Έβαλα λίγη γεύση σε μια κατσαρόλα και έβγαλα το μειλίχιο, ξέρω ότι ο παππούς μου θα έπαθε έμφραγμα αν έβγαζα έναν κυνηγό', 
            'Ξέρω ότι ο παππούς μου θα έπαθε έμφραγμα αν έβγαζα έναν κυνηγό'
        ],
        'answer': ['Greek', 'Greece']
    },
    'Mongolian': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Учир нь та бүгд програмтай танилцах хэрэгтэй Би том хүн, намайг поп гэж дууд', 
            'Тэд зүгээр л намайг урсгал, зээтүү, баглаа боодолтой шоу авсныг мэдэж байгаа', 
            'Таны амьдрал хэрхэн илчлэгдэж байгааг мэдэж байгаа ч би сонгосон амьдралынхаа төлөө тэр золиослолыг хийдэг', 
            'Гэхдээ Кентаки мужид сургуулиуд хаагдсан тул цас ороход би дуртай', 
            'Гэхдээ та үнэхээр зөвлөгөө авахыг хүсч байгаа үед хошигноход хэцүү байдаг, микрофонд хүрэх болгондоо алтанд хүрэх ямар байдаг вэ'
        ],
        'answer': ['Mongolian', 'Mongolia']
    },
    'Bosnian': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Ali teško je zbijati šale kada stvarno želiš savjet mislim, kako je dodirnuti zlato svaki put kad dodirneš mikrofon', 
            'Budući da svi trebate pogledati aplikaciju Ja sam odrastao čovjek, zovi me tata', 
            'Traže plakate sa mojim likom, znaju ko me traži', 
            'Jednom u životu, dok ne kažem da želim to dvaput jedinstveno, znaj da je sve moje', 
            'Moj sin mora naučiti da je oproštenje usamljeni put, kolijevke po njegovoj volji vole kućice na motoru'
        ],
        'answer': ['Bosnian', 'Bosnia']
    },
    'English': {
        'question': "Which language is this phrase from?",
        'sentences': [
            'Man down, call an amberlamps, tell him, "Breathe, bro"', 
            'Money trees is the perfect place for shade, and that\'s just how I feel', 
            'Everybody gon\' respect the shooter, but the one in front of the gun lives forever *(The one in front of the gun, forever)*', 
            'You are now watching the throne, don\'t let me get in my zone', 
            'No one man should have all that power, the clock’s ticking, I just count the hours'
        ],
        'answer': ['English', 'english', 'england', 'England']
    },


};